[{"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I assume you are talking about a pacman frog .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assume\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"There are a lot of genetics at play between a Sussex and Silkie , so the offspring would vary in appearance .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"vary\", does the participant \"offspring\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Dr. Obina told me that his office closed at noon and that I should call him on Monday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"Obina\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had a routine surgery for an ingrown toenail .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"surgery\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I wish that I had n't done this .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wish\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I knew a cat that died in its sleep aged 21 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"knew\", does the participant \"cat\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The situation appears to be even worse in Mississippi .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"appears\", does the participant \"situation\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"oh god is there an agenda .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"is\", does the participant \"agenda\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Winter defied his own board and Gov. Gray Davis when he filed a 50 - page request to remove the caps , records and interviews show .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"defied\", does the participant \"Winter\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The US Marines took most of Fallujah Wednesday , but still face pockets of resistance .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"took\", does the participant \"Marines\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Fried rice has NO flavor , it literally taste like water .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"rice\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They make up excuses in hopes to confuse their policy holders with misinformation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"make\", does the participant \"They\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i emailed you saaaaaam .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"emailed\", does the participant \"i\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The last wolf was killed in Yellowstone National Park in 1943 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"wolf\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The IPN report examines commercial fish species , but it neglects important non-commercial animals , such as seals and polar bears .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"neglects\", does the participant \"animals\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I like to imagine the thought processes going on in W 's head if he were to actually read the letter , but it is hard to picture him actually reading this letter .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"picture\", does the participant \"him\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They wanted to brainwash them and control them . ''\"\nQuestion: In the event \"brainwash\", does the participant \"them\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The storm threatened oil installations in the Gulf of Mexico where about one - quarter of US oil operations are based .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"threatened\", does the participant \"installations\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"they have their own website which you can easily find using any search engine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"website\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had a sampler of IPA , Brawler , Love Stout & ESA .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He knows what he s doing .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"knows\", does the participant \"He\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"According to some reports , Zawahiri is thought by intelligence to be somewhere near the border of Pakistan and Afghanistan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"thought\", does the participant \"Zawahiri\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Yeah you got ta burn it .. that s the only way\"\nQuestion: In the event \"got\", does the participant \"you\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"EVERYTHING IN HERE SEEMS TO AMAZE ME !!!\"\nQuestion: In the event \"SEEMS\", does the participant \"EVERYTHING\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I wish all happy holidays , and moreso , peace on earth .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wish\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"This means that I could be away from the office for several days and miss a message entirely , because it would have expired and disappeared by the time I returned .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"miss\", does the participant \"message\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"She has to iron her pants on the driveway .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"has\", does the participant \"She\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"( News assistant Bobby Bender recalls the letter containing the items to have been addressed to The Sun . )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"recalls\", does the participant \"letter\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The reports say she is suspected of having been a member of Al Qaeda 's \" Chemical Wire Group . \"\"\nQuestion: In the event \"suspected\", does the participant \"she\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I doubt the very few who actually read my blog have not come across this yet , but I figured I would put it out there anyways .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"figured\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Police said Bernard confessed to detectives that he had sex with a young girl in November 2002 and admitted to knowing about sexual acts involving children and a dog that occurred at Hosanna Church .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Police\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He vacated the FWS decision to downgrade the wolf 's status .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"vacated\", does the participant \"He\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"yea i guess but rabbits a easily escape a pen or another rabbit could get in there and that rabbit could be the opposite gender .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"escape\", does the participant \"rabbits\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"As much fun as they are , I figured we would probably do some different things than what you have planned for them .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"figured\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I enjoyed your recent e-mail but was sorry to hear about your dad .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enjoyed\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The painting is based upon the hymn called , ' A Charge to Keep . '\"\nQuestion: In the event \"based\", does the participant \"painting\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They worked for me and I hope they worked for you !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"hope\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He checked out what I needed to have done told me what needed be fixed before he did any work and did great repair work .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"checked\", does the participant \"He\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They have unbeatable price in town and deliver on time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"They\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Sanctuary serves delicious , somewhat healthy food in a great restaurant / fast food style .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"serves\", does the participant \"Sanctuary\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I used to tan down the street before I was referred to this place by one of my friends .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"referred\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"An analysis of 65 bird species in the United Kingdom shows about one - third are laying their eggs four to seven days earlier than they did 25 years ago .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"laying\", does the participant \"eggs\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The hijacker Ahmed Alhaznawi appears to have contracted cutaneous anthrax in Afghanistan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"contracted\", does the participant \"anthrax\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I started this page to help with my boredom .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"started\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think he could 've done more to assuage my concerns by giving me concrete facts .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I know it can take a while for results and did n't expect a miracle , but after 2 months I felt like it was not entirely worth the cost / time .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"know\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I loved the car so we began negotiating my trade - in and the price of the 09 XF .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"began\", does the participant \"we\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They indicated they could use Steve 's help face to face at some point .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"indicated\", does the participant \"They\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I sent this to Mary last week .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sent\", does the participant \"this\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a new born daughter and she helped me with a lot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"daughter\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The Rock revolution happened in the Sixties ( 6 , number of the Beast ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"happened\", does the participant \"revolution\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" My first thought was to push it away , \" he said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"push\", does the participant \"it\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I needed a part for my appliance , the cost was very high so I said never mind , paid the fee and called a local business for a second quote .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"paid\", does the participant \"fee\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Marly asked me to respond to you .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"asked\", does the participant \"Marly\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"At the time , guardsmen were required to accumulate a minimum of 50 points to meet their yearly obligation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"meet\", does the participant \"obligation\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"His one - day mission vaulted his communist homeland into the elite circle of spacefaring nations - Russia and the United States - that can launch and sustain humans in space .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"vaulted\", does the participant \"mission\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a parakeet named Cookie . :P\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"parakeet\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Both towns have airports that are served regularly from the larger cities such as Sao Paulo , Rio de Janeiro and Buenos Aires .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"airports\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a bit of experience watching the usual assembly line .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Only Irish coffee provides in a single glass all four essential food groups : alcohol , caffeine , sugar and fat .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provides\", does the participant \"coffee\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Many point to the trillion spore concentration as extraordinary .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"point\", does the participant \"Many\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The owners of Bowtie manged to add something new while preserving what was already there .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"manged\", does the participant \"owners\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" They can freely write anything they like about our prophet , but if one raises doubts about the Holocaust he is either fined or sent to prison , \" he added .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"raises\", does the participant \"one\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I knew a cat that died in its sleep aged 21 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"cat\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In Biloxi , 30 people were reported dead in one block of flats which was hit by a 9 m ( 30 ft ) \" storm surge \" .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reported\", does the participant \"people\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The initial reservoir reports estimate reserves of 80 - 120 million barrels of sour crude and they estimate initial production to be 40,000 bpd starting in 1Q 2003 .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"estimate\", does the participant \"reports\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Another problem is that sometimes bad eggs will fungus and the fungus will spread out and kill all the eggs .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kill\", does the participant \"eggs\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Sanctuary serves delicious , somewhat healthy food in a great restaurant / fast food style .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"serves\", does the participant \"food\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The Commission 's hearings begin tomorrow at 10 AM ( PST ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"begin\", does the participant \"hearings\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He described Allawi 's face as that of a f*ed horse and he dismissed the whole government as a band of thieves and traitors .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"dismissed\", does the participant \"government\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In addition to my other comments on the Mid Market Power Form , I think you should add a forward contract rep .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i have a Mature male and female they are together a lot but never laid eggs as far as i know can anyone help me figure out how to make them mate\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"i\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Birds eat and sleep with their flock , not predators .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"eat\", does the participant \"Birds\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a day stop - over in San Francisco and my wife want to see some of the key sites .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"the guy came on time and did n't take any breaks , he went straight to work and finished the job efficiently and promptly !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"came\", does the participant \"guy\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I guess that tells you a lot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"guess\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I spoke with Jeff Hodge yesterday regarding the additional language from Peoples regarding Audit Rights .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"spoke\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In June and July of 1973 , he accumulated 56 points , enough to meet the minimum requirement for the 1973 - 1974 year .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"accumulated\", does the participant \"he\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Pioneers were assigned numbers , which were included on all cheques , enabling the campaign to keep track of who raised how much . )\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assigned\", does the participant \"numbers\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Pakistani officials claim there are as many as 42 RAW agents based in Kandahar and another 12 in Jalalabad .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"claim\", does the participant \"officials\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Some board members pushed to have Winter removed , but there were concerns such action would lead to more chaos , the governor 's spokesman Maviglio said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"removed\", does the participant \"Winter\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The problem with this argument is that Bush lacked the experience necessary to be president when he ran in 2000 , so this sort of cheap shot just hoists him by his own petard .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ran\", does the participant \"he\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The name was derived from the founder 's name Dr. Michael Cowpland .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"derived\", does the participant \"name\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i use UTH's on all of my burrowing snakes .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"use\", does the participant \"i\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My cat had a seizure yesterday and was ill .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"cat\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had a dead battery last week and called this company since they were the closest they had very quick service for a Monday morning , thanks again guys .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They provide an emotional infrastructure for atrocities .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"provide\", does the participant \"infrastructure\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"As religious people , clergy and lay leaders , we are mandated by faith to stand for justice in our common civic life .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"mandated\", does the participant \"we\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have extensive experience as a technical leader in the design and development of modeling and simulation software products , mostly for the oil and gas pipeline industry .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"experience\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Tangipahoa Parish sheriff 's deputy Christopher Blair Labat , 24 , was booked Tuesday on one count of aggravated rape and one count of crime against nature .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"booked\", does the participant \"Labat\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I had to get a permit here , it was cool\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Newer semi-automatic wangs have a rail built into the receiver under the shaft .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"wangs\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Al - Sharq al - Awsat reports that a key eyewitness in the trial of Saddam Hussein for a 1982 massacre at Dujail has died .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"died\", does the participant \"eyewitness\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I think that this is for you since I do n't know any of these people .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"think\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I took the original piece of metal and rigged it to make due since I had to complete the job .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"complete\", does the participant \"job\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"You need a background in law enforcement .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"background\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I wish all happy holidays , and moreso , peace on earth .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wish\", does the participant \"holidays\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" I 'm pretty suspicious of making broad generalizations , \" however , he cautioned .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cautioned\", does the participant \"he\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The main reason I wrote this post is to ask anyone reading this if they know of some way I can help put a stop to this Cat Holocaust .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wrote\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He said the main aim of the subpoenas will be to determine whether collusion occurred to \" fix \" prices , which would violate federal trade laws .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"violate\", does the participant \"laws\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The clerics demanded talks with local US commanders .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"demanded\", does the participant \"clerics\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The dealer wanted $ 1300 to fix that and another $ 1500 to fix some other things .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wanted\", does the participant \"$\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The US chose to ally itself with such groups as the Supreme Council for the Islamic Revolution in Iraq , whose 15,000 - strong Badr Corps paramilitary was trained by the Iranian Revolutionary Guards .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"ally\", does the participant \"itself\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Allawi 's aged cousin and the man 's wife and daughter - in - law were abducted and guerrillas threaten to behead them if the Fallujah compaign is not stopped .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"behead\", does the participant \"them\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" The governor believes it was the defining moment , when what was a mounting problem turned into an instant crisis , \" Maviglio said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Maviglio\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have 3 children there and they are the Best .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"children\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We had to throw out about 80 percent of our meals because the food tasted so horrible .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"throw\", does the participant \"percent\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They have the best Egg Drop Soup I have ever tasted .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tasted\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Upon the same day he conquered Darius , won a great victory at sea , & died the same day .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"conquered\", does the participant \"Darius\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Mark Elliott tells me that you drafted some trader guidelines ( physical and financial ) for the London traders .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tells\", does the participant \"Elliott\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Guerrillas killed an engineer , Asi Ali , from Tikrit .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"Guerrillas\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a few how to videos for DIY 35 mm film in a 120 camera on my YouTube channel :\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I enjoyed my tour and i am looking for adventure tour and India heritage tours for valuable .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"enjoyed\", does the participant \"tour\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Disney cruises offer 24 - hour room services , and the crews are ready to serve you the way you like .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"offer\", does the participant \"cruises\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"A Yellowstone wolf was found dead , hit by a car , on a Colorado highway last year , several hundred miles from home .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"found\", does the participant \"wolf\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Bush asked for permission to go to Alabama to work on a Senate campaign .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"asked\", does the participant \"Bush\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a concern that the Enron optionality bug could bite us on the backside with that one .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"concern\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Xinhua reports that a wide range of Iraqi political forces on Tuesday condemned Sharon 's murder of Sheikh Ahmed Yassin , a religious leader of Hamas , the day before .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reports\", does the participant \"Xinhua\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Dr. Mann killed our pet\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"pet\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The people abandoned their farms and religious sites and the ground they stood on became moorland .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"abandoned\", does the participant \"people\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They have a customer for life in us !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"customer\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They needed someone that could convince the jury they had been able to see all relevant documents in CIA files on Wilson .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"convince\", does the participant \"someone\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The advisor kept me up to date and informed on the progress of my vehicle .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"kept\", does the participant \"advisor\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"She had her cards memorized as well as everyone else s ( when you play you 'll see why you can know everyone else s hands ! ) .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"play\", does the participant \"you\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"i reccomend you to go and enjoy their wonderful hospitality .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"reccomend\", does the participant \"you\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Police in the Indian capital Delhi say they have arrested the suspected co-ordinator and financier of last month 's deadly bomb blasts in the city .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arrested\", does the participant \"they\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Family owned and operated makes sure the atmosphere is relaxed and the food home - cooked with style .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cooked\", does the participant \"food\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I was told to leave a restaurant because I ordered water with my meal ( apparently this is \" washing down \" your food \" ) and not ordering wine .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Dignitaries condemn the act but visit her bereaved family and the money flows .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"condemn\", does the participant \"act\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a concern that the Enron optionality bug could bite us on the backside with that one .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"concern\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"My friend and I were to stay here for a girls night , catch up on our lives evening .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"were\", does the participant \"friend\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Mark Elliott tells me that you drafted some trader guidelines ( physical and financial ) for the London traders .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"drafted\", does the participant \"guidelines\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"they all need love and attn , food , proper surroundings etc .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"they\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We sued Houston Casualty last year but I do n't recall making any bad faith claims .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sued\", does the participant \"Casualty\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"These animals have the misfortune to produce a substance that is useful in the manufacture of perfume .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"animals\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"China launched Shenzhou VI , its second manned spacecraft , early today in northwest China 's Gansu Province .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"launched\", does the participant \"China\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" We applaud China 's space achievements , \" NASA spokesman Allard Beutel said Tuesday .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Beutel\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They both had pools for kids and adults .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"had\", does the participant \"pools\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" It was about how he could humiliate her the most , \" prosecutor Dean Mandros said in closing arguments .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Mandros\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I need to have a form filled out that says I do n't have health insurance coverage through Enron .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"need\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" I find it troubling that a candidate for president in our country -- the world 's oldest democracy -- would characterize the military takeover as \" good news , \" Gore said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Gore\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I have a concern that the Enron optionality bug could bite us on the backside with that one .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Based on specific intelligence inputs , Army arrested Ghulam Mohiuddin Lone , a LeT man , from Doda district .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"arrested\", does the participant \"Army\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"That indicates that they thrive in different water chemistries .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"indicates\", does the participant \"That\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They had a room with a $ 99 rate , which I booked .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"booked\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Two vaunted economists - one a Nobel Prize winner and the other a nationally renowned budget expert - have analyzed the data at hand and put a price tag on the Iraq occupation .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"have\", does the participant \"analyzed\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"there 's these little like bait worms at jack s . petshoppe .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"'s\", does the participant \"worms\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Guerrillas threatened to assassinate Prime Minister Iyad Allawi and Minister of Defense Hazem Shaalan in retaliation for the attack .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"threatened\", does the participant \"Guerrillas\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"\" In retrospect , we should have told them , '' Robinson said .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"said\", does the participant \"Robinson\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"He told us to stop by the salon and then he will tell us the price .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"us\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I get that careless teenager kind of treatment from some of their staff ... perhaps they should hire more serious adults to help serve / cook .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"get\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The letter bombs were sent in connection with the treatment of the Egyptian islamists imprisoned for the earlier attack on the WTC and a related plot .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"sent\", does the participant \"bombs\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The next day , the federal commission killed the new pricing plan .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"killed\", does the participant \"plan\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Ben made another announcement on March 28 , 2005 :\"\nQuestion: In the event \"made\", does the participant \"Ben\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We wanted to see the sun - and we also got much more !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"wanted\", does the participant \"We\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Attached are my resume and an addendum covering academic & consulting experience .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"Attached\", does the participant \"resume\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I told Paul that you called him yesterday so abruptly because you did n't want to waste his time while you got tests done for arthritis .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"told\", does the participant \"I\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"They tried to run my credit score as less as possible so it wo n't hurt my score .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"tried\", does the participant \"They\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"One of the students indicated that he is interested in a summer internship .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"indicated\", does the participant \"One\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"It is this circle that makes sure that women remain inferior , that democracy is unthinkable and that exposure to the outside world is minimal .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"remain\", does the participant \"women\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Four guys around a large square open hibachi cook your food , and when it 's finished a server brings it to your table .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"cook\", does the participant \"guys\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"We love our new roof !\"\nQuestion: In the event \"love\", does the participant \"We\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"I detect the hissing lisp of the lying serpent in this article .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"detect\", does the participant \"lisp\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"These look fine to me .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"look\", does the participant \"These\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"Exxon Mobil released nonessential staff from two giant Texas plants .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"released\", does the participant \"staff\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"In Baghdad Kadhim Talal Husain , assistant dean at the School of Education at Mustansiriyah University , was assassinated with his driver in the Salikh district .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"assassinated\", does the participant \"Husain\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"The pictures are broadcast at a rate of about 60 Hz , which is how fast they need to move for us to see them as a moving , flawless picture .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"broadcast\", does the participant \"pictures\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "No"}, {"prompt": "Answer this yes-no question about the following sentence.\nSentence: \"SCALIA filed a dissenting opinion , in which THOMAS and ALITO joined .\"\nQuestion: In the event \"filed\", does the participant \"SCALIA\" act on purpose?\nAnswer: ", "correct_value": "Yes"}]